const { MultipleChoiceQuestion } = require("../question.model.v1");

const multipleChoiceQuestions = [
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of the following are examples of figurative language?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 3,
    answers: ["Metaphor", "Simile", "Alliteration", "Onomatopoeia"],
    correctAnswers: ["Simile", "Alliteration"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of these words are synonyms for 'happy'?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 2,
    answers: ["Joyful", "Elated", "Gloomy", "Ecstatic"],
    correctAnswers: ["Joyful", "Elated"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "grammar",
    questionText: "Which of the following are Shakespearean plays?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 3,
    answers: ["Macbeth", "The Great Gatsby", "Hamlet", "To Kill a Mockingbird"],
    correctAnswers: ["Macbeth", "Hamlet"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of these are examples of non-fiction genres?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 2,
    answers: ["Biography", "Science Fiction", "Memoir", "Historical Fiction"],
    correctAnswers: ["Biography", "Memoir"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of the following are examples of literary devices?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 3,
    answers: ["Foreshadowing", "Irony", "Punctuation", "Allusion"],
    correctAnswers: ["Foreshadowing", "Irony", "Allusion"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText:
      "Which of these words are commonly used as transitional phrases?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 2,
    answers: ["However", "Therefore", "Quickly", "Nevertheless"],
    correctAnswers: ["However", "Therefore"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of the following are examples of tone in writing?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 3,
    answers: ["Sarcastic", "Blue", "Optimistic", "Tall"],
    correctAnswers: ["Sarcastic", "Blue"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eec10a67b1859ef8d717e1",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of these are examples of poetic forms?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 3,
    answers: ["Sonnet", "Haiku", "Essay", "Villanelle"],
    correctAnswers: ["Sonnet", "Haiku", "Villanelle"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText:
      "Which of the following are examples of narrative point of view?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 2,
    answers: [
      "First Person",
      "Third Person Limited",
      "Past Tense",
      "Omniscient",
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["First Person", "Third Person Limited"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of these are elements of a story's plot?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 2,
    answers: ["Rising Action", "Climax", "Setting", "Resolution"],
    correctAnswers: ["Rising Action", "Climax", "Resolution"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "vocabulary",
    questionText: "Which of the following are literary devices?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 3,
    answers: ["Metaphor", "Simile", "Paragraph", "Alliteration"],
    correctAnswers: ["Metaphor", "Simile", "Alliteration"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "vocabulary",
    questionText: "Which of these are types of figurative language?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 3,
    answers: ["Personification", "Hyperbole", "Punctuation", "Onomatopoeia"],
    correctAnswers: ["Personification", "Hyperbole", "Onomatopoeia"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "vocabulary",
    questionText: "Which of the following are parts of speech?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 2,
    answers: ["Noun", "Verb", "Sentence", "Adjective"],
    correctAnswers: ["Noun", "Verb", "Adjective"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "grammar",
    questionText: "Which of these are types of poetry?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 3,
    answers: ["Limerick", "Prose", "Ballad", "Free Verse"],
    correctAnswers: ["Limerick", "Ballad", "Free Verse"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "grammar",
    questionText: "Which of the following are examples of text structures?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 3,
    answers: [
      "Cause and Effect",
      "Compare and Contrast",
      "Dialogue",
      "Chronological",
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Cause and Effect",
      "Compare and Contrast",
      "Chronological",
    ],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of these are types of conflict in literature?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 3,
    answers: [
      "Man vs. Nature",
      "Man vs. Society",
      "Man vs. Punctuation",
      "Man vs. Self",
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Man vs. Nature", "Man vs. Society", "Man vs. Self"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of the following are examples of genres?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 2,
    answers: ["Mystery", "Science Fiction", "Paragraph", "Romance"],
    correctAnswers: ["Mystery", "Science Fiction", "Romance"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of these are types of characterization?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 3,
    answers: ["Direct", "Indirect", "Alphabetical", "Dynamic"],
    correctAnswers: ["Direct", "Indirect", "Dynamic"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of the following are examples of rhetorical devices?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 3,
    answers: ["Ethos", "Pathos", "Logos", "Mythos"],
    correctAnswers: ["Ethos", "Pathos", "Logos"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of these are elements of a story's setting?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 2,
    answers: ["Time", "Place", "Characters", "Atmosphere"],
    correctAnswers: ["Time", "Place", "Atmosphere"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "general",
    questionText: "Which of the following are examples of literary movements?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 4,
    answers: ["Romanticism", "Modernism", "Capitalism", "Postmodernism"],
    correctAnswers: ["Romanticism", "Modernism", "Postmodernism"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "vocabulary",
    questionText: "Which of these words are synonyms for 'ephemeral'?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 5,
    answers: ["Transient", "Fleeting", "Eternal", "Evanescent"],
    correctAnswers: ["Transient", "Fleeting", "Evanescent"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "grammar",
    questionText:
      "Which of the following sentences contain a dangling modifier?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 4,
    answers: [
      "Walking down the street, the trees were beautiful.",
      "Having finished the assignment, the TV was turned on.",
      "The dog wagged its tail when it saw its owner.",
      "To improve your health, exercise should be done regularly.",
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Walking down the street, the trees were beautiful.",
      "Having finished the assignment, the TV was turned on.",
      "To improve your health, exercise should be done regularly.",
    ],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "vocabulary",
    questionText: "Which of these words are examples of onomatopoeia?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 4,
    answers: ["Buzz", "Whisper", "Loud", "Sizzle"],
    correctAnswers: ["Buzz", "Whisper", "Sizzle"],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
  {
    type: "multiple_choice",
    section: "grammar",
    questionText:
      "Which of the following sentences use the subjunctive mood correctly?",
    instruction: "Select all that apply.",
    difficulty: 5,
    answers: [
      "I wish I was taller.",
      "If I were you, I would accept the offer.",
      "The teacher insisted that the student does his homework.",
      "It is essential that he be on time.",
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "If I were you, I would accept the offer.",
      "It is essential that he be on time.",
    ],
    isPublic: true,
    createdBy: "66eda220f1577aa9a314ab30",
  },
];
async function seedMultipleChoiceQuestions() {
  try {
    const result = await MultipleChoiceQuestion.insertMany(
      multipleChoiceQuestions
    );
    return result;
  } catch (error) {
    console.error(error);
  }
}
module.exports = { multipleChoiceQuestions, seedMultipleChoiceQuestions };
